A Guide to the W. W. LaPrade and Brothers Records, 1803-2001 (bulk 1900-1970)
Library of Virginia
- Series X. Field Book/Diaries, 1901-2000., Extent: 156 boxes. (Box 189-344)
  - Book Number 859-865 - Various, 1956-1959. (Box 258)
  - Book Number 866 - D. M. Lea, 1957. (Box 258)
  - Book Number 867 - Various, 1956-1958. (Box 258)
  - Book Number 868-869 - Various, 1956-1959. (Box 259)
  - Book Number 870 - Ridgeview, 1957. (Box 259)
  - Book Number 871-879 - Various, 1957-1960. (Box 259)
  - Book Number 880-881 - Various, 1957-1959. (Box 260)
  - Book Number 882 - Hechler Village, 1957. (Box 260)
  - Book Number 883 - Southside Plaza, 1957-1960. (Box 260)
  - Book Number 884-885, 887-888, 892-894 - Various, 1957-1972. (Box 260)
  - Book Number 896 - Hechler Village, 1958-1959. (Box 260)
  - Book Number 897, 899-909 - Various, 1958-1962. (Box 261)
  - Book Number 910-911 - Various, 1958-1959. (Box 262)
  - Book Number 912 - Hechler Village, 1958. (Box 262)
  - Book Number 914 - Various, 1958. (Box 262)
  - Book Number 915 - College of William and Mary, 1959. (Box 262)
  - Book Number 916-922 - Various, 1958-1960. (Box 262)
  - Book Number 923-925, 927-934 - Various, 1957-1966. (Box 263)
  - Book Number 935 - Reynolds Metals, 1958-1960. (Box 263)
  - Book Number 937-948 - Various, 1958-1967. (Box 264)
  - Book Number 949-960 - Various, 1959-1966. (Box 265)
  - Book Number 961 - Various, 1959. (Box 266)
  - Book Number 963 - Willow Lawn Apartments, 1960. (Box 266)
  - Book Number 964-973 - Various, 1959-1962. (Box 266)
  - Book Number 974-985 - Various, 1960-1962. (Box 267)
  - Book Number 986-987 - Various, 1960-1962. (Box 268)
  - Book Number 988 - Commonwealth Sand and Gravel, 1960. (Box 268)
  - Book Number 989-993 - Various, 1960-1963. (Box 268)
  - Book Number 994 - Commonwealth Sand and Gravel, 1960-1962. (Box 268)
  - Book Number 995-997 - Various, 1960-1961. (Box 268)
  - Book Number 999-1010 - Various, circa 1960-1961. (Box 269)
  - Book Number 1011-1022 - Various, 1961-1962. (Box 270)
  - Book Number 1023-1029 - Various, 1961-1964. (Box 271)
  - Book Number 1030 - Tappahannock, Gwynnfield, 1961-1964. (Box 271)
  - Book Number 1031-1034 - Various, 1961-1962. (Box 271)
  - Book Number 1035-1046 - Various, 1961-1972. (Box 272)
  - Book Number 1047 - Westover Apartments, 1962. (Box 273)
  - Book Number 1048-1056 - Various, 1962-1968. (Box 273)
  - Book Number 1057 - Commonwealth Sand and Gravel, 1962-1963. (Box 273)
  - Book Number 1058 - Various, 1962. (Box 273)
  - Book Number 1059-1068 - Various, 1962-1968. (Box 274)
  - Book Number 1069-1070, 1072-1080 - Various, 1962-1971. (Box 275)
  - Book Number 1082-1092 - Various, 1962-1978. (Box 276)
  - Book Number 1093-1104 - Various, 1963-1974. (Box 277)
  - Book Number 1105 - Commonwealth Sand and Gravel, circa 1963. (Box 278)
  - Book Number 1106-1116 - Various, 1963-1975. (Box 278)
  - Book Number 1117-1128 - Various, 1963-1978. (Box 279)
  - Book Number 1129-1140 - Various, 1964-1977. (Box 280)
  - Book Number 1141-1152 - Various, 1964-1972. (Box 281)
  - Book Number 1153-1162 - Various, 1964-1968. (Box 281a)
  - Book Number 1163 - Apartments, 1965. (Box 281a)
  - Book Number 1164-1172 - Various, 1965-1984. (Box 282)
  - Book Number 1173 - Hechler Village Section 5, 1965-1966. (Box 282)
  - Book Number 1174-1175 - Various, 1965-1971. (Box 282)
  - Book Number 1176-1184 - Various, 1965-1981. (Box 283)
  - Book Number 1185 - Hechler Village, Sears, 1965-1966. (Box 283)
  - Book Number 1186-1187 - Various, 1965-1971. (Box 283)
  - Book Number 1188-1199 - Various, 1965-1974. (Box 284)
  - Book Number 1200-1201 - Hechler Village, 1966-1975. (Box 285)
  - Book Number 1202-1211 - Various, 1965-1971. (Box 285)
  - Book Number 1212 - Blue Cross Building, McKinney Drilling Co., circa 1967. (Box 285)
  - Book Number 1213-1214 - Various, 1966-1976. (Box 286)
  - Book Number 1215 - Hechler Village, 1967-1969. (Box 286)
  - Book Number 1216 - Various, 1966-1967. (Box 286)
  - Book Number 1217 - Hechler Village Section 2 1966-1967, 1966-1967. (Box 286)
  - Book Number 1218-1224 - Various, 1966-1970. (Box 286)
  - Book Number 1225 - Various, 1965-1966. (Box 287)
  - Book Number 1226 - Oakhurst Section 4, 1966-1968. (Box 287)
  - Book Number 1227 - Various, 1967-1971. (Box 287)
  - Book Number 1228 - Hechler Village, 1966-1968. (Box 287)
  - Book Number 1229 - Hechler Village Shopping Center, 1966-1968. (Box 287)
  - Book Number 1230-1233 - Various, 1966-1976. (Box 287)
  - Book Number 1234 - Oakhurst, 1967-1970. (Box 287)
  - Book Number 1235-1236 - Various, 1967-1969. (Box 287)
  - Book Number 1237-1240A - Various, 1966-1974. (Box 288)
  - Book Number 1241 - Dunedin, 1967-1968. (Box 288)
  - Book Number 1242 - Various, 1968. (Box 288)
  - Book Number 1243 - Federal Reformitory, Petersburg, Va, 1967-1969. (Box 288)
  - Book Number 1244 - Various, 1967. (Box 288)
  - Book Number 1245 - "Maryfield" Tappahannock, 1967-1976. (Box 288)
  - Book Number 1246-1247 - Various, 1967-1970. (Box 288)
  - Book Number 1248-1250 - Various, 1967-1969. (Box 289)
  - Book Number 1251 - Camelot, 1967. (Box 289)
  - Book Number 1252 - Various, 1968-1974. (Box 289)
  - Book Number 1253 - Westmoor, 1968-1969. (Box 289)
  - Book Number 1254 - Various, 1967-1983. (Box 289)
  - Book Number 1255 - Fort Hell, 1967-1968. (Box 289)
  - Book Number 1256-1258 - Various, 1967-1978. (Box 289)
  - Book Number 1259-1262, 1264-1265 - Various, 1967-1973. (Box 290)
  - Book Number 1266 - Herman November, 1967-1969. (Box 290)
  - Book Number 1267-1268, 1270-1272 - Various, 1967-1977. (Box 290)
  - Book Number 1273-1281 - Various, 1968-1978. (Box 291)
  - Book Number 1282 - Hechler Village, 1968-1970. (Box 291)
  - Book Number 1283 - Various, 1967-1968. (Box 291)
  - Book Number 1284 - Richmond Coliseum, 1968-1974. (Box 291)
  - Book Number 1285-1296 - Various, 1968-1986. (Box 292)
  - Book Number 1297-1308 - Various, 1968-1990. (Box 293)
  - Book Number 1309-1314 - Various, 1969-1981. (Box 294)
  - Book Number 1315 - Berkeley Manor, 1969-1976. (Box 294)
  - Book Number 1316-1320 - Various, 1973. (Box 294)
  - Book Number 1321 - S. Perkins, R. Westwood Winfree, Atty., 1969-1977. (Box 295)
  - Book Number 1322-1325 - Various, 1969-1971. (Box 295)
  - Book Number 1326 - Luck Corp., 1969-1973. (Box 295)
  - Book Number 1327-1328 - Various, 1969-1977. (Box 295)
  - Book Number 1329 - Chesterfield County School Board, 1970-1972. (Box 295)
  - Book Number 1330 - Stonehenge, 1970. (Box 295)
  - Book Number 1331 - Various, 1969-1975. (Box 295)
  - Book Number 1333 - Stonehenge, 1969-1970. (Box 295)
  - Book Number 1332,1334-1337 - Various, 1970-1978. (Box 296)
  - Book Number 1338 - East Avenue Apartments, 1970-1971. (Box 296)
  - Book Number 1339-1342 - Various, 1970-1972. (Box 296)
  - Book Number 1343 - Chippenham Hospital, circa 1971. (Box 296)
  - Book Number 1344 - Various, 1970-1972. (Box 296)
  - Book Number 1345-1348 - Various, 1970-1977. (Box 297)
  - Book Number 1349 - Greenleigh/Coventry Gardens, circa 1971. (Box 297)
  - Book Number 1350-1355 - Various, 1970-1977. (Box 297)
  - Book Number 1356 - Various, 1971-1977. (Box 298)
  - Book Number 1357 - Beechwood Farms, 1971-1972. (Box 298)
  - Book Number 1358 - Chelsea, 1971. (Box 298)
  - Book Number 1359-1367 - Various, 1971-1976. (Box 298)
  - Book Number 1368-1371 - Various, 1971-1975. (Box 299)
  - Book Number 1372 - Richmond Industrial Interport, 1972. (Box 299)
  - Book Number 1373-1374 - Various, 1971-1976. (Box 299)
  - Book Number 1375 - Fair Oaks Terrace, 1972-1973. (Box 299)
  - Book Number 1376-1377 - Various, 1971-1973. (Box 299)
  - Book Number 1378-1385 - Various, 1972-1976. (Box 300)
  - Book Number 1386 - Richmond Industrial Interport, 1972-1973. (Box 300)
  - Book Number 1387-1389 - Various, 1972-1974. (Box 300)
  - Book Number 1390-1394 - Various, 1972-1984. (Box 301)
  - Book Number 1395 - Huntington Hills, 1972-1974. (Box 301)
  - Book Number 1396 - Arch Road Apartments, 1972-1985. (Box 301)
  - Book Number 1397 - Chelsea, 1972-1973. (Box 301)
  - Book Number 1398-1401 - Various, 1972-1978. (Box 301)
  - Book Number 1402 - Various, 1973-1974. (Box 302)
  - Book Number 1403 - Richmond Industrial Interport, 1973-1977. (Box 302)
  - Book Number 1404 - 8th and Main, 1973. (Box 302)
  - Book Number 1405-1408 - Various, 1973-1976. (Box 302)
  - Book Number 1409 - Chelsea, 1973. (Box 302)
  - Book Number 1410-1411 - Various, 1973-1976. (Box 302)
  - Book Number 1413-1414 - Various, 1973-1974. (Box 303)
  - Book Number 1415 - Medical College of Virginia-Virginia Commonwealth University, 1973-1975. (Box 303)
  - Book Number 1416 - Various, 1974. (Box 303)
  - Book Number 1417 - Chelsea, 1973-1979. (Box 303)
  - Book Number 1418 - Fair Oaks Apartments, 1972-1974. (Box 303)
  - Book Number 1419 - Various, 1973-1975. (Box 303)
  - Book Number 1420 - Jarrett Apartments, 1973. (Box 303)
  - Book Number 1421-1422 - 8th and Main, 1973. (Box 303)
  - Book Number 1423-1424 - Various, 1973-1975. (Box 303)
  - Book Number 1425-1427 - Various, 1973-1976. (Box 304)
  - Book Number 1428 - 8th and Main, 1973-1974. (Box 304)
  - Book Number 1429-1430 - Various, 1973-1975. (Box 304)
  - Book Number 1431 - 8th and Main, 1974. (Box 304)
  - Book Number 1432 - Various, 1974-1978. (Box 304)
  - Book Number 1433 - 8th and Main, 1974. (Box 304)
  - Book Number 1434 - Various, 1974-1984. (Box 304)
  - Book Number 1435 - 8th and Main, 1974. (Box 304)
  - Book Number 1436 - Various, 1974-1975. (Box 304)
  - Book Number 1437-1438 - Various, 1974-1976. (Box 305)
  - Book Number 1439 - Lone Star, 1974-1977. (Box 305)
  - Book Number 1440 - 8th and Main, 1974. (Box 305)
  - Book Number 1441 - Gayton Green, 1974-1976. (Box 305)
  - Book Number 1442-1443 - Various, 1973-1975. (Box 305)
  - Book Number 1444 - 8th and Main, 1974-1975. (Box 305)
  - Book Number 1445 - Various, 1974-1975. (Box 305)
  - Book Number 1446 - 8th and Main, 1974. (Box 305)
  - Book Number 1447 - 8th and Main [2 books], 1974-1988. (Box 306)
  - Book Number 1448-1455 - Various, 1974-1978. (Box 306)
  - Book Number 1456-1466 - Various, 1975-1985. (Box 307)
  - Book Number 1467 - Walmsley Terrace Apartments, 1975-1976. (Box 307)
  - Book Number 1468-1469 - Various, 1975-1977. (Box 307)
  - Book Number 1468-1469 - Various, 1975-1977. (Box 307)
  - Book Number 1470 - Ruffin Road Apartments, 1975-1978. (Box 308)
  - Book Number 1471-1472 - Various, 1975-1976. (Box 308)
  - Book Number 1473 - Federal Reserve Bank, 1976-1977. (Box 308)
  - Book Number 1474-1476 - Various, 1975-1976. (Box 308)
  - Book Number 1477 - K-Mart, 1976-1977. (Box 308)
  - Book Number 1478-1479 - Various, 1976-1979. (Box 308)
  - Book Number 1480 - Bexley, 1976-1977. (Box 308)
  - Book Number 1481-1483 - Various, 1976-1987. (Box 308)
  - Book Number 1484 - K-Mart, Meadwood, 1976-1977. (Box 309)
  - Book Number 1485 - Various, 1976-1977. (Box 309)
  - Book Number 1486 - Commerce Acres, Pruitt, 1976-1977. (Box 309)
  - Book Number 1487-1489 - Various, 1976-1978. (Box 309)
  - Book Number 1490 - Bexley, 1976-1978. (Box 309)
  - Book Number 1491-1493 - Various, 1976-1978. (Box 309)
  - Book Number 1494 - Brookfield, Southern States, 1976-1977. (Box 309)
  - Book Number 1495-1497 - Various, 1976-1978. (Box 309)
  - Book Number 1498-1511 - Various, 1976-1979. (Box 310)
  - Book Number 1512-1523 - Various, 1977-1991. (Box 311)
  - Book Number 1524-1535 - Various, 1977-2000. (Box 312)
  - Book Number 1536-1537 - Various, 1978-1979. (Box 313)
  - Book Number 1538 - Marbro Construction Co., 1978-1979. (Box 313)
  - Book Number 1539-1545 - Various, 1978-1986. (Box 313)
  - Book Number 1546 - McGuire Hospital, 1978. (Box 313)
  - Book Number 1547 - Various, 1978-1982. (Box 313)
  - Book Number 1548-1549 - Various, 1978-1980. (Box 314)
  - Book Number 1550 - McGuire Hospital, 1978-1979. (Box 314)
  - Book Number 1551 - Various, 1978-1982. (Box 314)
  - Book Number 1552-1553 - Randolph-Macon College, 1978-1984. (Box 314)
  - Book Number 1554 - Various, 1978-1989. (Box 314)
  - Book Number 1555 - McGuire Hospital, 1979. (Box 314)
  - Book Number 1556-1557 - Various, 1979-1980. (Box 314)
  - Book Number 1558 - McGuire Hospital, 1979. (Box 314)
  - Book Number 1559-1561 - Various, 1979-1981. (Box 315)
  - Book Number 1562 - McGuire Hospital, 1979. (Box 315)
  - Book Number 1563-1565 - Various, 1979-1984. (Box 315)
  - Book Number 1566 - McGuire Hospital, 1979. (Box 315)
  - Book Number 1567-1568 - Various, 1979-1983. (Box 315)
  - Book Number 1569 - McGuire Hospital, 1979. (Box 316)
  - Book Number 1570 - Various, 1979-1983. (Box 316)
  - Book Number 1571-1572 - Pumping Station Bench Marks and Levels, 1979. (Box 316)
  - Book Number 1573 - Various, 1979. (Box 316)
  - Book Number 1574-1575 - McGuire Hospital, 1979. (Box 316)
  - Book Number 1576 - Various, 1979-1980. (Box 316)
  - Book Number 1577 - Various, 1979-1984. (Box 316)
  - Book Number 1578 - McGuire Hospital, 1979-1980. (Box 316)
  - Book Number 1579 - Various, 1979-1981. (Box 317)
  - Book Number 1580 - McGuire Hospital, 1979-1980. (Box 317)
  - Book Number 1581 - Various, 1980-1984. (Box 317)
  - Book Number 1582 - G & H Sewer Line # 11, 1980. (Box 317)
  - Book Number 1583-1584 - McGuire Hospital, 1980. (Box 317)
  - Book Number 1585 - Various, 1980. (Box 317)
  - Book Number 1586 - McGuire Hospital, 1980. (Box 317)
  - Book Number 1587 - Various, 1980-1997. (Box 317)
  - Book Number 1588 - Finished Sewer Line III, 1980-1981. (Box 317)
  - Book Number 1589 - Various, 1980. (Box 317)
  - Book Number 1590 - Philip Morris, 1980-1981. (Box 317)
  - Book Number 1591 - Various, 1980-1997. (Box 318)
  - Book Number 1592-1600 - Various, 1980-1984. (Box 318)
  - Book Number 1601-1603 - Various, 1981-1984. (Box 319)
  - Book Number 1604 - Farm Fresh- Broad St., 1981-1985. (Box 319)
  - Book Number 1605-1610 - Various, 1981-1996. (Box 319)
  - Book Number 1611-1614 - Various, 1981-1991. (Box 320)
  - Book Number 1615 - Woodman West, 1981-1982. (Box 320)
  - Book Number 1616 - Rockville, 1981-1987. (Box 320)
  - Book Number 1617-1618 - Various, 1981-1983. (Box 320)
  - Book Number 1619 - Rockville, 1982. (Box 320)
  - Book Number 1620 - Various, 1982-1984. (Box 320)
  - Book Number 1621-1623 - Various, 1982-1984. (Box 321)
  - Book Number 1624 - Bluffs, 1982-1983. (Box 321)
  - Book Number 1625-1630 - Various, 1982-1989. (Box 321)
  - Book Number 1631-1633 - Various, 1983-1984. (Box 322)
  - Book Number 1634 - Botany Woods, 1983-1986. (Box 322)
  - Book Number 1635 - Various, 1983-1984. (Box 322)
  - Book Number 1636 - Bryan Park, 1983-1985. (Box 322)
  - Book Number 1637-1640 - Various, 1983-1989. (Box 322)
  - Book Number 1641 - 12/Main, 1983. (Box 323)
  - Book Number 1642-1648 - Various, 1984-1998. (Box 323)
  - Book Number 1649 - Lone Star- Dock St., 1984-1985. (Box 323)
  - Book Number 1650-1652 - Various, 1984-1993. (Box 323)
  - Book Number 1653-1655 - Various, 1984-1989. (Box 324)
  - Book Number 1656 - School # 2, 1984-1985. (Box 324)
  - Book Number 1657 - Stony Point Apartments, 1984-1985. (Box 324)
  - Book Number 1658 - Leigh St., 1984-1985. (Box 324)
  - Book Number 1659 - Various, 1985. (Box 324)
  - Book Number 1660 - STP, 1985. (Box 324)
  - Book Number 1661 - School, 1985. (Box 324)
  - Book Number 1662 - Bland Ridge ABC Corp., 1985-1986. (Box 324)
  - Book Number 1663-1664 - Various, 1985-1989. (Box 324)
  - Book Number 1665-1667 - Various, 1985-1987. (Box 325)
  - Book Number 1668 - Blue Star Water, 1985-1987. (Box 325)
  - Book Number 1669-1672 - Various, 1985-1991. (Box 325)
  - Book Number 1673 - Bland Ridge, 1985-1987. (Box 325)
  - Book Number 1674 - Various, 1985-1987. (Box 325)
  - Book Number 1675-1676 - Various, 1985-1990. (Box 326)
  - Book Number 1677 - North Woods, 1986-1987. (Box 326)
  - Book Number 1678-1679,1681-1685 - Various, 1986-1993. (Box 326)
  - Book Number 1686-1687 - Various, 1986-1988. (Box 327)
  - Book Number 1688 - 2n Church # 1 [Glen Allen Baptist Church], 1986-1987. (Box 327)
  - Book Number 1689-1693 - Various, 1986-1992. (Box 327)
  - Book Number 1694 - Wistar Center, 1987-1989. (Box 327)
  - Book Number 1695 - Various, 1987. (Box 327)
  - Book Number 1696-1697 - Various, 1987-1991. (Box 328)
  - Book Number 1698 - Shockoe Plaza and Medical College of Virginia, 1987-1988. (Box 328)
  - Book Number 1699-1701 - Various, 1987-1990. (Box 328)
  - Book Number 1702 - UPS [United Parcel Service], 1987-1991. (Box 328)
  - Book Number 1703 - North Woods, 1987-1988. (Box 328)
  - Book Number 1704-1707 - Various, 1987-2000. (Box 328)
  - Book Number 1708-1711 - Various, 1987-1992. (Box 329)
  - Book Number 1712 - Shockoe Plaza, 1988-1990. (Box 329)
  - Book Number 1713-1716 - Various, 1988-1994. (Box 329)
  - Book Number 1717 - Wilde Lake Apartments, 1988-1990. (Box 329)
  - Book Number 1718 - Wilde Lake Apartments, 1988. (Box 330)
  - Book Number 1719 - Catalpa, 1988-1992. (Box 330)
  - Book Number 1720 - Airport Army and Navy, 1988-1992. (Box 330)
  - Book Number 1721 - Riverfront Plaza, 1988-1990. (Box 330)
  - Book Number 1722-1725 - Various, 1988-1993. (Box 330)
  - Book Number 1726 - E. R. Carpenter, 1989. (Box 330)
  - Book Number 1727 - Various, 1989-1991. (Box 330)
  - Book Number 1728 - Short Pump, 1989-1990. (Box 331)
  - Book Number 1729 - Strum, 1989-1999. (Box 331)
  - Book Number 1730-1736 - Various, 1989-2000. (Box 331)
  - Book Number 1737 - East Gate Mall, 1989-1991. (Box 331)
  - Book Number 1738-1739 - Various, 1990-1991. (Box 331)
  - Book Number 1740-1751 - Various, 1990-1999. (Box 332)
  - Book Number 1752-1756 - Various, 1991-1992. (Box 333)
  - Book Number 1757 - Liesfeld, 1991-1992. (Box 333)
  - Book Number 1758 - Various, 1991-1993. (Box 333)
  - Book Number 1759 - Gas Line I, 1991-1992. (Box 333)
  - Book Number 1760 - Colonial, 1991. (Box 333)
  - Book Number 1761 - Various, 1992. (Box 333)
  - Book Number 1762 - RF & P [Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad], 1992-1994. (Box 333)
  - Book Number 1763 - Various, 1992-1994. (Box 333)
  - Book Number 1764 - Various, 1992-1993. (Box 334)
  - Book Number 1765 - 5th Street, Gas Line II, 1992-1996. (Box 334)
  - Book Number 1766-1768 - Various, 1991-1993. (Box 334)
  - Book Number 1769 - Liesfeld II, 1992. (Box 334)
  - Book Number 1770-1771 - Various, 1992-1993. (Box 334)
  - Book Number 1772 - U. T. S. [Union Theological Seminary], Ethyl Corp., 1992-1994. (Box 334)
  - Book Number 1773 - V. C. U. [Virginia Commonwealth University] Linden St., 1992-1995. (Box 334)
  - Book Number 1774 - Various, 1993. (Box 334)
  - Book Number 1775 - M. C. V. [Medical College of Virginia], 1992-1995. (Box 334)
  - Book Number 1776 - R. K. & K., 1992-1993. (Box 335)
  - Book Number 1777 - Audubon, 1992-1993. (Box 335)
  - Book Number 1778 - R. K. & K., 1992-1997. (Box 335)
  - Book Number 1779 - Ukrop's, 1993. (Box 335)
  - Book Number 1780 - 11th [and] Clay [Streets], 1993-1995. (Box 335)
  - Book Number 1781 - Various, 1993. (Box 335)
  - Book Number 1782 - Ukrop's, 1993-1994. (Box 335)
  - Book Number 1783, 1785 - Various, 1993-1996. (Box 335)
  - Book Number 1786 - Around Randolph, 1993-2000. (Box 335)
  - Book Number 1787 - Henricus Park, 1993-1995. (Box 335)
  - Book Number 1788 - Various, 1993-1996. (Box 335)
  - Book Number 1789-1792 - Various, 1993-1995. (Box 336)
  - Book Number 1793 - D. P. U., Bon Air, Avis, 1993-1996. (Box 336)
  - Book Number 1794 - Vinci-Randolph, 1993-1995. (Box 336)
  - Book Number 1795 - U. T. S. [Union Theological Seminary], 1993-1996. (Box 336)
  - Book Number 1796 - Port of Richmond, 1994-1996. (Box 336)
  - Book Number 1797 - Grove, Lakeside, 1994-1996. (Box 336)
  - Book Number 1798 - Various, 1994-1996. (Box 336)
  - Book Number 1799 - Gas Line, R. K. & K., 1994-1999. (Box 336)
  - William and Mary, 1925. (Box 337)
  - William and Mary, 1926. (Box 337)
  - Battlefield Park, circa 1943. (Box 337)
  - Stanley Dam, Road on Wastefield, circa 1945. (Box 337)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Co.- DuPont Hopewell Transmission Line, circa 1920. (Box 337)
  - Massaponax Sand and Gravel Corp., 1939. (Box 337)
  - Suffolk-Winfall Transmission Line, Levels, No. 1, circa 1926. (Box 337)
  - Suffolk-Winfall Transmission Line, Levels, No. 2, circa 1926. (Box 337)
  - Suffolk-Winfall Transmission Line, Transit Book No. 1, circa 1926. (Box 337)
  - Suffolk-Winfall Transmission Line, Transit Book No. 2, circa 1926. (Box 337)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Co., Richmond-Fredericksburg Transmission Line, No. 1, circa 1926. (Box 338)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Co., Richmond-Fredericksburg Transmission Line, No. 2, circa 1926. (Box 338)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Co., Richmond-Fredericksburg Transmission Line, Levels, No. 1, circa 1926. (Box 338)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Co., Richmond-Fredericksburg Transmission Line, Levels, No. 2, circa 1926. (Box 338)
  - Appomattox River Survey, Levels, 1925. (Box 338)
  - Appomattox River Survey, Levels, 1925. (Box 338)
  - Appomattox [River Survey], 1926. (Box 338)
  - Appomattox [River] Survey, P.L. Sta1848+75 to 2095+63, Baseline to River from Sta. 781 to Sta. 1069, circa 1925. (Box 338)
  - Appomattox River Survey, Base Line, circa 1925. (Box 338)
  - Appomattox [River] Survey, Property Line, North Side, circa 1925. (Box 338)
  - Appomattox River Survey, Contour Line, North Side, No. 1, circa 1925. (Box 338)
  - Appomattox River Survey, South Property Line, No. 2, circa 1926. (Box 339)
    This book had a photograph of a surveying party circa 1926 pasted inside the front cover. The photograph was removed for preservation purpose, but images of it in place are included in this box.
  - Appomattox River Survey, Property Line, South Side, Sta. 3+80 to 1520+64, 1926. (Box 339)
  - Appomattox River Survey, Individual Property Lines, South Side, Baseline to River North Side, circa 1926. (Box 339)
  - Appomattox River Survey, Contour in Dinwiddie Co., Sta. 0+00 to Sta. 1185+62, South Side, Book 1, circa 1925. (Box 339)
  - Appomattox River Survey, Contour Line, North Side, No. 3, circa 1925. (Box 339)
  - Appomattox River Survey, Contour Line, North Side, No. 2, circa 1925. (Box 339)
  - Appomattox River Survey, South Side Contour, Book 2, circa 1926. (Box 339)
  - Appomattox [River] Survey, South Side Contour, Book 3, circa 1926. (Box 339)
  - Appomattox River [Survey], Contour Line on South Side, Also Topography of Dam Site, 1926. (Box 339)
  - State Rifle Range, Camp Site, 1922-1923. (Box 339)
  - State Rifle Range, Virginia Beach, 1924. (Box 339)
  - State Rifle Range, Virginia Beach, 1926-1930. (Box 339)
  - Surry Lumber Co., Book 00, 1908-1910. (Box 340)
  - Surry Lumber Co., Book 1, 1909. (Box 340)
  - Surry Lumber Co., Book 2, 1909. (Box 340)
  - Surry Lumber Co., Book 2, 1909. (Box 340)
  - Westham, 1939. (Box 340)
  - Westham, 1937. (Box 340)
  - Book Number - "A", 1901-1902. (Box 340)
  - Unidentified, 1907-1909. (Box 340)
  - Unidentified, 1916. (Box 340)
  - Unidentified, 1919. (Box 340)
  - Unidentified, 1921. (Box 340)
  - Unidentified, 1923-1924. (Box 340)
  - Unidentified, 1929. (Box 340)
  - Unidentified, 1935. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1935. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1935. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1935-1936. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1936. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1936. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1936. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1936. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1936. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1936. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1936-1937. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1937. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1937. (Box 341)
  - Unidentified, 1937. (Box 342)
  - Unidentified, 1938. (Box 342)
  - Unidentified, 1938. (Box 342)
  - Unidentified, 1939. (Box 342)
  - Unidentified, 1939. (Box 342)
  - Unidentified, 1939-1940. (Box 342)
  - Unidentified, 1940. (Box 342)
  - Unidentified, 1940. (Box 342)
  - Unidentified, 1940. (Box 342)
  - Unidentified, 1940-1941. (Box 342)
  - Unidentified, 1940-1941. (Box 342)